# Julie Gordon

468 Third Road, Miami, FL 87654 j.gordon@myemail.com (432) 123-4567

Organized and dedicated health and social services manager with 12 years experience coordinating healthcare provision. Talent for employee development and motivation with an excellent reputation for creating effective education programs. Superb organization skills and ability to oversee large caseloads under time pressure.

## Key Skills

- Relationship management
- Provision planning
- Staff training and mentorship
- Problem-solving
- Time management and organization

## **Professional Experience**

#### Health and Social Services Manager

UnitedHealth Group, Miami, FL j June 2017 - Present

- Create and deliver professional development programs to a team of 20+ health coordinators to extend their knowledge of external resources, increasing employee retention by 65% over 2 years
- Supervise coordinators managing up to 80 cases at once, reviewing care plans and organizational pathways to ensure seamless and appropriate provision
- Act as an escalation point for the most complicated cases, resolving 98% of problems within the target deadlines
- Build and maintain relationships with external agencies to facilitate ongoing support following patient discharge

#### Case Management Specialist

BCFS Health and Human Services, Miami, FL j July 2009 - July 2017

- Managed a caseload of up to 15 clients simultaneously, prioritizing tasks strategically to tight and inflexible timeframes
- Handled calls from clients experiencing a health crisis and made prompt referrals for emergency care, resolving 87% of time-critical cases within 24 hours
- Generated appropriate healthcare plans based on insights gleaned from initial assessments
- Completed detailed service reports, exceeding submission targets by 68% in 2016

### Education

#### Bachelor of Science in Social Work

Barry University, Miami Shores, FL, September 2003 - June 2007

#### Master of Social Work

University of Miami, Miami Shores, FL, September 2007 - June 2009